[Nie Feng]
[Yan Ruo Bing]
[Meng Xiao Die]
[Meng Lan Yan]
[Yan Ru Yu]
♪A long sword danced among colorful lights♪
♪I watched you disappear at the horizon♪
♪Our first encounter never came around again♪
♪I wished to be by your side,
yet our love was defeated by rumors♪
♪I withered away in the passage of time♪
♪Watching the moments stumble along♪
♪Laughing at the hypocrisy of the world♪
♪But the wine and tears are true♪
♪So many rights and wrongs♪
♪Words from the red moon♪
♪Lying in front of you♪
♪Who could sever the chains of fate?♪
♪Who could tell the good from evil
and end the chaos?♪
♪Smitten for a lifetime,
lost in a millennium-long dream♪
♪Unforgettable is this deep love♪
♪Smitten for a lifetime,
lost in a millennium-long dream♪
♪Unforgettable is this deep love♪
♪As the falling flower wakes the wind,
snow turns into smoke♪
[The Peak of True Martial Arts]
[Episode 24]
Have you heard
that the other day,
the Si family invited 20
Bodiless Renewal Realm Warriors
from the Kou family in Qingxuan City
to the Nie family,
but none of them came out?
You mean the transcendental family
in Qingxuan City?
No way.
There is a world of difference
in the ability of the two families.
The warriors of the Kou family didn't come out.
Besides, even the Si family has been
removed from a list in Qinghe Bay.
I heard that there was a Transcendental Strong Warrior
in the Kou family in Qingxuan City.
Alas, if that's the case,
he will seek vengeance.
Yeah, he will surely do that.
I just wonder if the Nie family can survive.
Everyone understands that,
so now all forces in Qinghe Bay
don't dare to be very close to the Nie family,
fearing that they will be
implicated in the future.
(With Nie Feng around, they're worried for nothing.)
The Kou family should know the news.
Before that Transcendental Strong Warrior comes,
I must hurry to speed up
the improvement of Cultivation.
(From Qingxuan City to Qinghe Bay,)
(it will only take one day to arrive downstream.)
(And it will only take one and a half days
to go back to Qingxuan City)
(from Qinghe Bay upstream.)
(Even if they stayed for half a day
at the Si family after that,)
(they should have come back
within three days at most.)
(Besides, if they got held up,)
(they should have had the message sent to me.)
(It's been over 5 days.)
(Why haven't the people I sent come back yet?)
Elder Hao Yang,
bad news.
The warriors who went to Qinghe Bay...
What's wrong with them?
They are all dead.
What?
All dead?
They are a good
20 Bodiless Renewal Realm Warriors
who are all the elite people
of Bodiless Renewal Realm of the Kou family.
Didn't Si Yang Fu say
there were only two Bodiless Renewal Realm
Warriors in the Nie family?
I sent 20 Bodiless Renewal Realm Warriors.
How could they be all dead?
I heard that on that day, Si Yang Fu
went to Nie's Residence with another
Bodiless Renewal Realm Warrior of the Si family,
Si Xing Yun, 100 elite people of the Si family,
and our 20
Bodiless Renewal Realm Warriors.
In the end, only nine people of the Si family
escaped from Nie's Residence,
but later they were chased and killed.
The others didn't come out alive.
Now the Si family has been eradicated
in Qinghe Bay.
No one knows what exactly happened
at Nie's Residence on that day.
Oh, right. I also heard
that the nine people
were all killed by the son
of the head of the Nie family, Nie Feng.
According to those witnesses,
I feel the moves Nie Feng used
are a bit like Transcendental Martial Arts.
Is he the Nie Feng that Kou Hong Yu and Kou Yu
waited at the Nie family?
Yeah.
He's quite weird.
I heard that he has suffered from Toxic Heat
since he was a kid,
so he can't cultivate his skills at all.
However, a few months ago, his Toxic Heat
suddenly disappeared.
(Besides, his cultivation speed improves
by leaps and bounds.)
(He once defeated Kou Yu's guard
who was in Blood Changing Realm)
(with the cultivation of Chakras Opening Realm.)
(Now he has even reached the later stage
of Bodiless Renewal Realm.)
(It's very unusual.)
I think Nie Feng must be the key figure.
Our warriors were very likely to die at his hands.
A man in the later stage
of Bodiless Renewal Realm
can defeat our 20
Bodiless Renewal Realm Warriors?
From what I've seen,
his ability
is far higher than his own cultivation.
You see, he can defeat Blood Changing Realm
just with Chakras Opening Realm.
Now he has reached the later stage
of Bodiless Renewal Realm.
His real ability
might have reached the realm
of True Martial Arts.
What matters more is his cultivation speed.
Even the intelligent disciples
of the major sects
in the world
can't become the Bodiless Renewal Realm Warriors
within just a few months.
I guess he must have
experienced something unusual.
I have to go to Qinghe Sect again
and invite Patriarch back as soon as possible.
Our family has such a disaster,
so the Nie family must pay the price.
[Kou's Residence]
(There are nine domains in Nine Domains Mainland.)
(Besides Yanhuang Domain
connecting eight domains,)
(the other eight domains are occupied
by the major eight sects.)
(They hold the principle that one sect
controls one domain.)
(Among them,)
(Pontiff Hao Tian's territory, Haotian Domain,)
(is divided into 13 prefectures.)
[Qingsu City]
(Places such as Qinghe Bay, Qingxuan City, and Qingsu City)
(are all part of Qingzhou Prefecture,
in the east of Haotian Domain.)
(Qinghe Sect is a large sect
in Qingzhou Prefecture.)
[Prince Kou Ding's Residence]
(The sect has close ties with Pontiff Hao Tian.)
(Its territories include)
(many cities that center on Qingsu City.)
Greetings, sir.
Thanks for your hard work.
What's wrong with him?
Here's the thing.
This time, he went all the way
to Qinghe City to buy things.
But the quality goods had been bought
by the Star Ocean Chamber of Commerce.
He only bought some inferior goods.
So he's in a very bad mood.
Mr. Kou.
What is it?
Someone from the Kou family wants to see you.
He's waited for you at your residence for 10 days.
Got it.
Although you're relaxed,
you will be furious
after hearing the news of the Kou family.
What did you say?
Please calm down.
How dare an ordinary martial arts family
do such a thing to my family!
I will wipe out the Nie family of Qinghe Bay.
I wonder when you intend to set out.
Of course now.
The one who can fly in the sky
is a Transcendental Strong Warrior.
Is he the Transcendental Patriarch
of the Kou family,
Kou Ding Hou?
My goodness, even the Transcendental
Strong Warrior is here.
Something bad will happen to the Nie family.
Where's Nie's Residence?
Within this half a month,
I take in Yuanling Stone every day
to improve my skills.
I've reached the peak of Bodiless Renewal Realm
and I can become bodiless.
As long as I finish changing bones,
I can enter True Martial Arts
from Ordinary martial arts
and become a Transcendental Strong Warrior.